Wow.
Well done.
You have reached the end of the course.
You must be feeling super amped.
Super excited.
Because if you got to this far, you've done super well.
I think you've done really well.
You've learned to make your own website from knowing nothing to building this amazing, amazing website
with two pages, links, images and now you can carry on by yourself learning as you go.
Absolutely.
This is just a start.
So what you've done so far is you've learned the basics.
You've learned how to take HTML code, put it together, your program, an HTML program now, and build
your first website.
You can have two pages, three pages, 20 pages, whatever you like.
It's a starting point.
This is where it begins.
But there's so much more.
There's more you can learn about HTML.
We hope you've given you the confidence to learn that and look out for other courses on HTML.
Then there are the other aspects.
Remember what we said?
HTML5 is made up of what HTML, CSS and what's the last one?
Come on, tell them JavaScript.
JavaScript.
Of course you knew that those three things are what HTML5 is about, and we will have courses coming
out shortly on those.
They probably there already, so check them out.
So it's been exciting.
We've loved having you.
Please reach out to us.
We want to hear your comments, talk to us in the discussions.
Got questions?
Ask us.
And please give us that five star review.
We want that.
And if it's not five star and there's something you don't like, let us know what it is.
Because part of our learning journey is improving.
We want to make it better and better, and we can only do that with your input.
So we value your comments.
We value being on the course.
Tell your friends if you enjoyed it.
We'd love to see you on one of our other courses as well, so don't forget to connect with us!
We've had a great fun.
We've enjoyed teaching you and all the best in your HTML journeys going forward.
Yeah, goodbye!
Have lots of fun.
Keep on learning.
See ya!